Okay, who'd like to start
us off with show-and-tell?
Stewie?
Yes, today I brought in
my mother's driver's license.
Now, if you look closely,
she's clearly drunk.
You could put a Breathalyzer up
to that photo
and she'd get a DUI.
Ha-ha, Stewie's naked!
What?!
Oh, my God!
Don't look! Don't look!
Cell phones down!
What the deuce?!
Stewie!
Run from the monster.
You might have to drive.
Thank you all so much
for coming this evening
to my very fancy dinner party.
Oh, my God!
I'm at Glenn Close's house!
You look very handsome tonight,
Stewie.
Well, thank you.
And you're the prettiest
of all the women I know
whose name is Glenn.
Everyone,
please finish your salads,
because our main course tonight
is...
boiled rabbit.
I-I don't... I don't get that.
It seems weird that I'd have
a joke in my own dream
that I don't get.
Oh, thank you so...
Quick, you're
almost on!
What? I'm on?
But I don't know any
of my lines!
♪ It seems today ♪
♪ That all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in
movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
(mumbling gibberish)
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
(mumbling gibberish)
♪ Pumpkin pie ♪
What the hell? Put
him on the bench.
Wait, please, no!
I just wasn't ready!
Don't worry.
We'll put you in soon.
Ho-ho-ho!
Is funny
because you won't be back!
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Wait, how did Joe get halfway up
those stairs?
Lois, get in here!
It's dark and I'm frightened!
I think they've got this thing
backwards.
Hey, wake up!
I had a bad dream, so now
your night has to be terrible.
Peter, Stewie's upset.
Scooch over so he
can sleep with us.
Oh, come on.
Are you serious?
Last time, he kicked me
all night.
And I got a big day tomorrow.
I got two shows.
All right, folks,
big treat for you today.
He's a little shy.
Put your hands together
for Sham-Peter!
I'm not shy! I'm angry!
I'm in constant pain!
This act has been condemned
by over 30 nations!
I'm gonna kill you all!
Ah, crap.
I can't sleep like this.
And now my mind is racin'.
Like, how does that candle
in Beauty and the Beast
sing so good?
I mean, the teapot I get,
'cause she's a girl. But
the candle, I don't under...
Oh, he's French. That's why.
Couch it is, I guess.
Oh, my God. The couch is gone.
Where the hell is...
Oh, that's right.
Couchella is this weekend.
Hey, man,
where you been?!
I just had sex with
a girl on her period!
Dude, that's not a brag!
So, how fat are you?
240? Nice.
Oh, Peter! What are
you doing down here?
Oh, hey, Brian. Stewie
kind of took over our bed,
so I'm looking
for a place to sleep.
Well, why don't you
go up to the attic?
I think there's even
a futon up there.
Huh. That's a great idea.
Geez, I'm glad you came along.
I'm gonna sleep better
than a cartoon sheriff.
I was in jail 'cause
I killed a bunch of old ladies.
And now that I'm out,
I'm gonna do it again.
Wow, Stewie,
you look exhausted.
Yeah, 'cause I was up super late
last night, beefing your mom.
My mom's dead.
Yeah, 'cause I
beefed her to death.
Whoa, what's your problem?
Why are you being such a jerk?
I'm sorry, Brian.
I had the absolute worst night.
I had a weird dream.
A frightening dream.
Yeah, Stewie,
that's called a nightmare.
Sounds like you must've had
your first one.
That's what a
nightmare is?
I thought "nightmare"
meant, like, being invited
to an apartment party.
Get a house if you
want to have a party.
I'm not going to a
party in an apartment.
Relax, it's no big deal.
People have nightmares
all the time.
Oh, no, Brian. I am not living
through that horror again.
In fact, I've decided
that from this day forward,
I shall never allow myself
to fall asleep again.
Come on, that's ridiculous.
How do you think
you're gonna do that?
I don't know.
Maybe I'll get a job
working the night
shift at a supermarket.
Hey, where's
the vegetable aisle?
Yeah, right, it's 2:00 a.m.
You're not here for vegetables.
Well, I got the
12 cucumbers.
What's wrong?
Just this guy at the...
Never mind.
Peter, we have a hamper.
Stop throwing your dirty clothes
in the toilet.
Peter?
Peter, where are you?
What's all this?
Oh, hey, Lois.
Welcome to the Pete Pad,
where the dancing's hot,
the drinks are hot...
Everything's
just freakin' hot.
What have you
done to the attic?
Well, when I slept up here
the other night,
I realized
what a great space it is.
So I dragged up some stuff and
turned it into a sweet hangout.
Even made it extra awesome
by stealing a real street sign.
I don't understand. What
are you gonna do up here?
Eh, mostly just burn the roof
of my mouth
on unevenly-heated
microwave burritos.
Now I'm busy, so close the floor
and get out of here.
All right, all right,
come on, Stewie.
You've got to stay awake.
I know what'll help.
I'll watch that preview channel
that always has
inconsistent volumes.
They're mother and daughter
but also best friends.
Catch Gilmore Girls
on Channel 367.
You can name your own price
for hotel rooms!
Help! Please!
Damn it! Why can't I move?!
Aah!
Stewie, you okay?
What happened?
I was just sitting here
on the couch and I had
another nightmare
about that horrible monster.
Okay, that's it.
I'm gonna help you get these
nightmares under control.
Really?
Oh, thank you, Brian.
And maybe I can help you
control your strange obsession
with eating
pencil erasers.
It's not an obsession.
Mmm, mmm, oh, yeah.
Oh, so rubbery. Mmm.
It's like a little
steak. Mmm, mmm.
Brian, you really should...
The world is small and
safe when I do this!
Okay, Stewie, I read the review
of a dream book on Amazon,
so I think I can help you.
Literally every other tab
is open to Lusty Matures.
Yup, that's what
it takes now.
Anyway, it says here
that most nightmares
are born of
subconscious fears.
So maybe if we make
a list of the things
you're most afraid of,
we can face and conquer
these fears together, and
then your nightmares'll end.
Huh, that's actually
a good idea.
Like the U.S. Army Reserves.
We're completely surrounded.
We need reinforcements.
You know who could
really bail us out?
Somebody who works five days
a week at Enterprise Rent-A-Car.
These new digs of yours
are pretty great, Peter.
Hey, I brought
construction paper and markers
in case you guys
want to draw breasts.
Cool. But before that, who's up
for another insulation fight?
I'm in.
Heck yeah.
Ha!
Gotcha!
Missed me.
Sneak attack!
What are you
doing up here?
I need you to take
the trash out.
You know what?
I'm gonna use this
Peter Doesn't Have to Take Out
the Trash coupon
that I got for my anniversary.
You gave that to yourself.
I don't know,
it says "official."
Oh, forget it,
I'll do it myself.
This whole attic
business is ridiculous.
Hey, guys, check it out.
I'm a lady.
Joe...
you hit a home run with
that, I want to try it.
All right, Stewie,
time to tackle your fears.
Now, it sounds like
you're scared of monsters.
So to help you get over it.
here's Frankenstein.
I'm Frankenstein.
I'm actually really nice.
There's no need
to be scared of me.
Seriously?
This is obviously
Chris in a costume.
Huh. Well, that
can't be possible.
Because here comes Chris
walking in the door right now.
Hey, hey, hey.
Here comes Chris Griffin,
a-roodly-toot-toot.
Yeah, okay,
whatever, Meg.
Meg?
You must be
talking about me,
a-roodly-toot-toot.
Do they all say
"a-roodly-toot-toot"?
A lot of them, yeah.
Chris, I'm putting
together a load of laundry.
You got anything?
Damn it, Peter.
Are you guys playing lawn darts
in the attic again?
No.
Yay, lawn darts!
Peter wins lawn darts.
She's dumb.
She got no idea.
All right, Peter,
that's enough.
It is time to
get out of...
What the hell?
Oh, yeah, we put Joe
in Stewie's old Jolly Jumper.
You told me this was
a paratrooper's harness.
Shut up, baby man.
That's it. This
is our home,
not some frat house for
you and your friends.
Now, I want you out
of this attic now.
No way, we ain't leaving.
We're having
too much fun up here.
Quagmire just showed us
his Eric McCormack impression.
There could be
no such thing.
Well, that's what I said,
but then he did it,
and I was like, "Oh, all right,
okay, yeah, kind of."
Fine. You like the
damn attic so much?
Then enjoy the attic!
Did... did she just
lock us in here?
It looks like it.
Guys, spin me back.
I didn't see what happened.
So, how'd it go last night?
Did we cure your nightmares?
No, not at all. They
were worse than ever.
Which is why I built this.
What the hell is that?
It's a Digital Dream Interface.
You see, once connected
to this device,
you will be able to enter
my sleeping mind, where
you will end these horrible
dreams once and for all.
I'm gonna do what?
What... what-what
does he want?
What is he saying?
I think he's saying
"a-roodly-toot-toot".
We just can't understand him
because of the way he talks.
Oh, no, no, I think
he just needs a ride home.
Stewie, you can't be serious.
Oh, I'm very serious.
You and I will place these
cranial impulse receptor caps
on our heads, I shall
begin my slumber, and...
And then this thing
will actually allow me
to enter your dream?
That's right, Brian.
I want you to come inside
me while I'm asleep.
Do-Don't... don't
say it like that.
And once you're in my
dream, your job is to stop
these nightmares by finding
that monster and killing him.
This isn't a job
for the meek, Brian.
When you get in there,
you've got to be hard.
Okay, but that
felt intentional.
All right,
let's get to it.
This is your receptor cap.
Over here is your REM monitor.
What's this thing do?
Oh, that's just a little
bike bell for fun.
I found it at the crosswalk
where those kids
got creamed the other day.
Anyway, let's get started.
Hello? Stewie?
Ah, you must be
Brian. I'm Glenn.
Yes, I know. You were
very mean in 101 Dalmations.
Thank you. Would you like
to do the Bristol Stomp?
♪ The kids in Bristol
are sharp as a pistol ♪
♪ When they do
the Bristol Stomp ♪
How does he even know this?
♪ Really somethin' when
they join in jumpin' ♪
He heard it once in the car.
Jeez, Lois
is really serious.
I can't believe
she left us up here all night.
Damn it, we got to do something.
Maybe if we just scream for help
someone'll hear us.
Help! Help! Help!
In case of a bear attack,
you should
A, lie down,
B, run downhill,
or C, stand your ground?
...and just because
of the roles I play,
people always assume
I'm very serious in real life.
Yeah, I could see that.
But I'm not.
I'm very capable
of being silly, too.
See, watch, I'll show you.
Fart.
I, uh... Did-did...
did you just say "fart"?
Yes, that's me
being rather silly.
Well, hello, Brian.
I say, what
brings you here?
Stewie, hey! I'm here
to find and kill the monster
that's been causing
all your nightmares.
Oh, that sounds
wonderful! Let's do it!
Oh, but real quick,
I'm just gonna turn
into Elmo for a second.
Hi, Brian!
Elmo speak bad English
on educational show!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Okay, I'm back.
Let's go.
This way to the
subconscious.
Oh, this seems rather pleasant.
Yeah.
Hey, you know, that Glenn Close
salad actually wasn't bad.
Yeah, a lot of my dreams
have pretty good salad.
Oh, no.
What?! Where are we?!
We're at the doctor!
Time for a baby shot
in your fanny!
Come give Grandpa a sloppy,
old-man, coffee kiss!
Would you like some candy?
Help me find my lost puppy?
I like your mouth and butt.
What the hell was that?!
Lois has painted a very
dark picture of abduction.
Adult stuff,
adult stuff, adult stuff.
The world is scary,
Scary people yelling in another
part of the world, adult stuff.
I wish Mom wouldn't watch
the news in front of me!
Coming up: a map with
a hurricane on it.
And you don't know
your states yet!
Aah! That one trip to the
petting zoo really messed me up!
I saw too much!
Stewie, look!
It's the monster!
Quick, Brian!
Kill it!
Oh, there you guys are.
I would've been here sooner,
but one of my legs is a snake
that's very hungry for mice.
Nice shot.
Get it? Shot?
All right, bye!
You did it, Brian!
You killed
the monster!
What the hell?!
It's me!
Oh, my God,
you're right!
But I... I don't understand.
Why am I the source
of your fears?
Huh. I'm
not sure.
Maybe this means
that deep down,
the thing I'm most afraid
of is disappointing you.
Me? Wh-Why do you care so much
about what I think?
Well, think about it.
You've been more of a
father figure to me
than the fat man ever
has been or ever will be.
Look, I know
I'm always busting your balls,
but it's just because you're
the only person in this house
whose judgment
actually matters to me.
Wow. Thanks, Stewie.
But listen, you-you never have
to worry about letting me down.
I'll always be proud of you.
In fact, I already am.
You are?
'Course I am.
I mean, you're only a baby,
and yet,
you're one of the most
amazing people I know.
Well, thank you, Brian.
Well, Stewie, seems like
my work here is done.
What's the best way
out of here?
Oh, yeah, no, that
one stays locked
until the overnight to Vegas
with my college
a cappella group.
Peter, I'm going
crazy up here.
We all are!
You got to talk to Lois!
Damn it, you're right.
Lois, let us out of here!
No way! You like it so much?!
Then you can rot up there
with your buddies!
Lois, so help me God,
if you don't let us out
right this second,
I'm gonna take a dump
on your wedding dress!
You wouldn't dare!
Don't test me. I'll do it!
We'll all do it!
Quagmire, pull down
your pants!
What?! I'm not doing that!
You leave my dress alone, Peter!
If it'll get us out of here,
I'll make a doodie on it.
What, are you nuts?!
I've been crowning
for six hours!
Cleveland's pants are off, Lois!
Here come mine!
This is happening!
Lois, they're not bluffing!
Open the door!
I miss Bonnie!
Damn it, Peter,
you hold that in!
I know you can!
You did it on the ferry
to Block Island!
Oh, my God, I'm gonna puke!
That's good! Puke on the dress!
Puke on the dress!
Aah, damn it!
Not all snake bites are lethal.
There! You happy?!
You were too late.
We pooed on the gown.
Ripped a big hole
in your ceiling, too.
I barfed on Peter's ass.
I-I don't know if it got
on the dress or not, Lois,
but I-I am... I am so sorry.
Yeah, this was all
a huge disaster.
Let's just agree that we both
went a bit too far, hmm?
I, uh... I might...
I might need two weeks off
from this friendship.
Stewie, you awake?
Did you have any nightmares?
I don't think so.
Did you get rid of the monster?
Sure did. Turned out
that monster was nothing more
than a manifestation
of your subconscious desire
not to disappoint me.
Apparently, I'm like
a father figure to you.
Okay. Wow. Somebody's
got a big head.
Stewie, I want you to know...
I'm very proud of you.
All right, that's...
that's awkward.
How-how am I supposed
to respond to that?
You are a good person.
Stop complimenting me.
"Oh, I sure hope the dog
approves of who I am."
I'm out of here, weirdo.
There's a wedding dress out here
covered in.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru